const STORE = [
    {
      question: "Who is the youngest of Ned Stark's children?",
      answers: [
        "Arya",
        "Sansa",
        "Bran",
        "Rickon"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
      question: "Who is Jon Snow's mother?",
      answers: [
        "Olenna Tyrell",
        "Lysa Arryn",
        "Lyanna Stark",
        "Cersei Lannister"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "What is Davos Seaworth's nickname?",
      answers: [
        "Sand Snake",
        "Hot Pie",
        "The Hound",
        "Onion Knight"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
      question: "Which character gets continually resurrected by Thoros of Myr after he dies?",
      answers: [
        "Jaquen H'ghar",
        "Beric Dondarrion",
        "Barristan Selmy",
        "Alliser Thorne"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "How does Gregor Clegane kill Oberyn Martell?",
      answers: [
        "crushes his skull",
        "poisons him",
        "strangles him",
        "cuts his head off"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "Which former ranger of the Night's Watch led an army of wildlings as the 'King-Beyond-the-Wall?",
      answers: [
        "Mance Rayder",
        "Tormund Giantsbane",
        "Craster",
        "Janos Slyut"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "What's the name of  the band of assassins that Arya Stark joins in Braavos?",
      answers: [
        "Sons of the Harpy",
        "Second Sons",
        "Faceless Men",
        "Brotherhood Without Banners"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is NOT a name of one of Daenerys Targaryen's dragons?",
      answers: [
        "Drogon",
        "Balerion",
        "Viserion",
        "Rhaegal"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "What are the \"house words\" of House Greyjoy?",
      answers: [
        "We Do Not Sow",
        "Unbowed, Unbent, Unbroken",
        "Winter is Coming",
        "Ours is the Fury"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "The Mad King was ",
      answers: [
        "Aerys II",
        "Robert Baratheon",
        "Rhaegar Targaryen",
        "King Joffrey"
        ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    }
];